You're my one and only bro.
From now on, I'll only listen to you.
I had my reasons for doing this.
Reasons?
What reasons?
I stole the crystals for my sister.
Your sister?
I did this just to make more money.
So my sister could live a better life.
My sister,
she grew up without a dad's love or a mom's care.
I worked my heart out.
Worked so hard to make money.
Just to give her a proper birthday celebration.
Am I wrong?
Your sister's birthday is coming?
But that doesn't seem to be the main issue here.
Then,
why don’t your parents care about her?
Aren’t you two siblings?
Bro,
you don’t know the full story.
It’s a long story.
Actually, my sister and I are half-siblings.
Her mom and my dad,
got divorced when she was little.
And my dad,
later met my mom,
and had me.
Meanwhile, her mom started a new family
and had another child.
So,
my sister was like a ball, being
passed around.
Passed around.
So,
my sister has always felt like an extra.
She’s had it that bad?
Only more,
never less.
Take good care of my sister in the future, okay?
Future brother-in-law.
Well, nothing else to say.
The misunderstanding has been cleared up.
I’ll head out now.
Bye, bro-in-law.
You're awake.
What's going on?
Such a fancy breakfast so early in the morning.
These...
are all prepared for you.
For me?
Qi Miao,
happy birthday!
If you hadn’t said anything, I would’ve forgotten it’s my birthday.
Thanks!
Come on, our relationship...
no need to say thank you.
Bro,
what’s going on between you and my sister now?
We’ve already reached...
Uh, the weather’s a bit dry.
Just eat your breakfast.
Sis,
we're all adults here.
What’s there to be shy about?
Shut your mouth.
Even eating can’t stop you from talking, huh?
Qi Miao,
should we...
take this chance on your birthday to invite your parents over?
That way, I can also get to meet them.
I think...
there’s no need for that.
But I haven’t met your parents yet.
I think it’s really necessary.
Is your eye twitching?
Uh...
You guys enjoy your breakfast.
I’ll head to work first.
Sis, Qi Miao,
why does it feel like she’s upset?
Bro,
be more confident.
Take out the 'feel like.’
I already told you,
parents are a sensitive topic for my sister.
But...
I just wanted to give her a happy birthday.
Celebrating someone’s birthday requires skill.
Come here.
Let me teach you.
Speak properly.
Of course, you need to prepare surprises for a birthday.
And the bigger the surprise, the better.
Surprise?
If you meet someone with the same energy as you,
and establish a connection,
then you should stay together your whole life,
until the end.
What's going on?
Why do I keep thinking about him?
It must be because this person is too annoying.
That has to be it.
No way.
Focus!
Work, work, work!
Bye-bye, bye-bye.
See you tomorrow!
Qi Miao.
I bring you a dance performance.
Happy
Birthday!
Qi Miao!
Happy Birthday!
You're so embarrassing me.
Alright.
Let's go.
It's just a pair of chopsticks.
You can arrange them however you want.
Unless you can make a flower out of them?
Don't you even know what quality of life means?
This pair of chopsticks shows your true nature.
What's wrong with my nature?
Even if my life isn't simple,
I am,
very down-to-earth.
Not like some people,
pretending to be aloof.
I’m really happy today.
Thank you.
As long as you're happy.
Who are you calling pretentious?
Say it again if you dare.
Every extra second I spend with you,
is pure torture.
So you don’t want to see me?
You can leave, Dad.
Why are you here? Just go!
Why aren't you leaving? You... Dad... Auntie.
Stop arguing, all of you.
I'll take care of this.
I'll do it.
Dad.
Mom.
Why are you here?
It's your birthday today.
Mom came over to celebrate your birthday.
Sweetheart.
Happy birthday.
Did you invite them?
Sis, happy birthday.
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday... Alright, alright.
Stop singing.
After dinner,
everyone goes back home.
Miao Miao.
What?
You're not even letting us eat?
This is for my daughter.
I'm giving it to her myself.
Here, eat.
I've checked this soup.
It's good for your health.
Thank you.
Xiao Hao.
Did you cook this whole dinner?
Yes, I did.
This young man is not only good-looking but also talented in cooking.
Miao Miao.
You really have good taste.
Mom!
Miao Miao.
Don't listen to your mom rambling.
When finding a boyfriend, looks aren't everything.
Character matters too.
Right?
What are you even saying?
Saying that,
how do you think Xiao Hao would feel?
It's okay.
Miaomiao,
early this morning,
Xiao Hao called us,
inviting us to celebrate your birthday.
It's very thoughtful of him,
really rare to see these days.
I think this young man is quite remarkable.
Miaomiao,
Dad is very pleased.
Dad,
we're just roommates.
Roommates?
Come on,
come on,
where are you from?
What do you do for a living?
Oh, sorry.
I haven't introduced myself yet.
I'm from Bluecore Star,
a Star Envoy of Bluecore Star.
Bluecore Star?
Never heard of it.
Is it some remote little town?
Far away?
Far.
Farther than you could ever imagine.
Miaomiao,
how far have you two progressed?
Auntie,
with my years of battlefield experience in love,
I can tell they've definitely already...
Qi Dongdong!
Why are you everywhere?
Even food can't shut you up, can it?
We've already established a connection.